http://www.ubt.com/privacy

Topic
- Any -Employee BenefitsManaging Your MoneyOnline InvestingBusiness Banking OnlineBuilding CreditOwning a HomeInvestingUBTgoRetirementEstate PlanningRunning a BusinessFraud PreventionCommunity Commitment
Main navigation
Personal
Column
Checking
Savings
Certificates of Deposit (CD)
Credit Cards
Personal & Auto Loans
Home Loans
Investments
Employer Programs
Online & Mobile Banking
View All
Column
Financial Privacy Resources
Offering you exceptional service, along with protecting your privacy, is important to us.  To understand what type of information we collect, and what we do with this information, please see our Privacy Notice. To opt out of sharing certain information with our affiliates, use the Financial Privacy Form.
Financial Privacy Notice
Financial Privacy Form
Union Bank & Trust Company Online Privacy Statement          Effective 7/15/2014
This Online Privacy Statement (“Statement”) describes the treatment of information that is provided or collected through any of Union Bank & Trust Company’s (“Union Bank”, “our”, “we”) online interfaces to which a copy of the Statement is posted.  This Statement includes all “Services” which inclusively refers to www.ubt.com (the “Website”), Applications we have placed on third party sites such as Facebook®, Twitter® and other social media sites, and our mobile applications (“Applications”).  This Statement also explains how we collect, use, and share information based on users’ interactions with online advertisements, both on the Services and on online interfaces owned by third parties.  This Statement does not govern our privacy practices offline or with respect to information that is not provided or collected through the Services.
For information on Union Bank’s offline privacy practices see our Financial Privacy Notice and your choice for opting-out of information sharing with our affiliates.
While this Statement describes how we treat information, please be aware additional terms and conditions may apply for certain parts of our Website and Applications.
Agreement to Statement
By using the Services you consent to this Statement.  You do have the choice to opt-out of certain tracking, please see “Online Tracking and Advertising” section below.
Types of Information We Collect through online Services
We collect two basic types of information through the Services – personal information and anonymous information.
“Personal information” refers to information that identifies a particular individual, such as information you provide on our forms, surveys, applications or similar online fields.  Examples include your name, address, telephone number, tax identification number, or account information.
“Anonymous information” means information that does not directly or indirectly identify a particular individual.  Examples may include information about your Internet browser, information collected through tracking technologies, demographic information that you provide to us.
“Location information” means information that may be collected by certain mobile applications that identifies your physical location.  This information may be collected from your mobile device’s location-aware features when you request certain services that are dependent on your physical location.
How We Collect Your Information
We collect personal information from you when you provide this information to us directly.  For example, when you apply for accounts through our Services, or register for an Application.
In addition, we may collect information about your activity on the Services automatically using tracking technologies, such as cookies.  For additional information, see the section entitles “Online Tracking and Advertising”.
How We Use Your Information
We may use information collected through the Services in order to, among other things:
Provide you with, or evaluate your eligibility for, products and services that you request from us
Communicate with you about your accounts or transactions with us
Send you important information regarding the Services
Allow you to participate in surveys, sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions, and to administer such promotions (note that these promotions may contain additional disclosures regarding our collection and/or use of your information)
Consistent with local law, required disclosures, and choices and controls that may be available to you:
Send you offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that may be of interest to you;
Personalize content and experiences on the Services;
Verify your identity and/or location (or the identity or location of your authorized representative) for security, fraud prevention and other risk control purposes; and
Provide you with advertising based on your activity on the Services and on third-party websites and applications.
Optimize or improve our products and services
Detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
Comply with our legal and regulatory obligations
How We Share Your Information
Please refer to Union Bank’s Privacy Notice.
Online Tracking and Advertising
We, along with certain service providers operating on our behalf, may collection information about your activity on the Services using tracking technologies, including:
Cookies.  Cookies are pieces of data stored on your device.  Browser cookies are assigned by a web server to the browser on your device.  When you return to a site you have visited before, your browser gives this data back to the server.  We use cookies that allow us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. Using Google Analytics we can see what content is popular on our Website, and strive to give you more relevant information.
Google AdWords.  Our Website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Union Bank Website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with this Statement, our own privacy policy (www.ubt.com/privacy) and Google’s privacy policy.  We restrict access and collection of information by advertising service providers for purposes other than assisting us with our advertising efforts.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page (https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en), and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by adjusting your browser’s cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
Linked Websites
The Services may contain links to third-party websites not controlled by Union Bank.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Services and to read the privacy policies and terms of use of any such websites that may collect your personal information.
Information Security and Preventing Identity Theft
Your privacy is important to Union Bank.  We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures that comply with federal law and industry standards, including network firewalls, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption for online sessions, dedicated security teams and secured files and buildings.  You have the responsibility to help us protect your accounts by never revealing your username, password or PIN to other individuals.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under the age of 13 through our website or online environment.  We request that such individuals do not provide personal information through the Services.  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without parental or guardian consent, he or she should promptly contact us and we will delete such information from our files.
Social Media Platforms
Union Bank may utilize various social media platforms, including Facebook® and Twitter®.  Please note any content you post to such social media platforms is subject to the applicable social medial platform’s terms of use and privacy policies, and is not in our control.
Changes to this Statement
From time to time, we may make changes to this Statement.  If we do make changes, we will update the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Statement.  We encourage you to review the Statement periodically to ensure you understand how we collect, use and share information through the Services. By continuing to use the Services following any changes, you are agreeing to accept the terms of the revised Statement.
